Collin Paradis

912 West Street, Ludlow, M.A. 413-523-2103 CollinParadis7@gmail.com

August 2018 - May 2019

April 2017 - August 2017

Highly motivated college graduate with a double major in Computer Information Technology (C.I.T) and Marketing with experience in website design and Information Technology. Enthusiastic about being a part of a team that provides I.T. solutions to an organization.

Education

Elms College Chicopee, MA Bachelors of Arts in Computer Information Technology & Bachelors of Arts in Marketing May 2019 Minor in Management GPA: 3.74

- NSF STEM Scholarship
- Magna Cum Laude

Tech Foundry Springfield, MA A fourteen-week comprehensive I.T career development program that focuses on June 2019

building the skills necessary to perform entry technical services. The program puts emphasis on professional development, proper documentation, and gaining real-world experience.

Skills

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, PHP, Ajax, C#, Java Programming Languages Operating Systems Windows 7-10, Windows Server 2016, Linux, Mac Software Office365, Active Directory, ConnectWise, VMware DHCP Client/Server, DNS, E-mail Server Networking

Experience

Freelance Web Designer Chicopee, MA

Town of Worthington, Salon Bocage, River Valley Rugby

January 2019 - Present Generate and design a website based on the business owners needs and

the concepts that they want portrayed. Maintain website by updating content, implementing new technology and monitoring performance.

Chicopee, MA Elms College

Technical Support Specialist Intern

- Troubleshot issues that faculty and students encounter including problems with performance, software, and peripherals.
- Utilized remote sessions to perform imaging of new computers and installation of software.
- Performed repairs on broken computers to make them functional again.

Chicopee, MA Elms College Web Designer Intern April 2018 - August 2018

Collaborated in a team to produce websites using HTML5, WordPress, and Wix that are standard compliant, SEO optimized, and multi-device.

- Performed front-end development for websites to improve functionality and user experience using HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Managed, maintained and updated existing websites for clients.

Volunteer Activities

Elms College Tech Committee, Member August 2017 - May 2019 January 2016 - May 2019 C.I.T Computer Lab Monitor, Volunteer